I saw somebody today telling me on this internet that wealthy people work and, and we can all be
billionaires if we work hard. First of all, we know that's rage bait and it's nonsense,
but I was like, no, wealthy people don't work. Their money works for them. And they were like,
no, they work really hard. You know, they sacrifice time from their family,
something that many of us wouldn't do. Let's cut it out. Let's cut it out.
Now, wealthy people are not people who are billionaires. Okay.
Typically either inherited that money or they exploit for that money.
The time that they are not with their families is by choice. It's because they enjoy the act of
exploitation. The, the, the, the world is their board game. We are the pieces.
So it's not work for them. Okay. It is literally an extracurricular activity that they do not have
to participate in, which is also why there are so many billionaire families that will tell you
that they do not operate like a family. They are dysfunctional. They are full of all types of
addicts, et cetera, et cetera. They are not any better off mentally than those who are struggling.
One, because money doesn't buy happiness, but two, because these billionaires are, you have to be,
the planet is literally dying and you're hoarding money and talking about fracking to get oil.
In the Arctic. You have to be a whole genocide is happening and fascism is sliding in. And
these folks, they're not like saying anything against this. They're not opposing this. No,
because they don't want to lose their billions. They're on tour selling thousand dollar tickets.
They're publicizing engagements. They're dropping albums. Some of which have weird,
shady, racist messaging. You have to be. The competition of capitalism is more engaging for
them than the protection of people. Do you understand what I'm saying? Billionaires.
Now, no, I am not poor, but I'm very far from wealthy and I do artwork and you can support it.
Head to AmandaSeals.com to get your tickets to the live stream performance and book release of my
latest work. What would the ancestors say?